Guide to the Lee Abbott Papers, circa 1965-2011 SPEC.RARE.CMS.0394
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Reviews and Essays, 1978-2009; Series 2
  - All Set About With Fever Trees by Pam Durban; Crazy Women by Jack Matthews; and Standing Room by Hollis Summers book reviews, manuscript draft, circa 1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Amanda/Miranda by Richard Peck book review, manuscript drafts and published copy in TWA Ambassador magazine, 1980 April (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Anyone seen the real McCoy" book review of The Autograph Man by Zadie Smith, published copy in The News & Observer, 2002 October 20 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - As Max Saw It by Louis Begley book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "Australia's Robin Hood leaves a legacy of truth to his daughter" book review of True History of the Kelly Gang by Peter Carey, published copy in The Herald, 2001 January 14 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "Bad Habits" essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "The Bed of Imaginary Love" review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - The Best American Short Stories edited by Joyce Carol Oates book review, manuscript drafts, circa 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "The Best of the Web" essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - "The Boston Story: Looking Out for No. 1" music essay, published copy in Crawdaddy magazine, 1978 December (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Campfires of the Dead by Peter Christopher book review, published copy in Southpoint magazine, 1990 January (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Carl Sandburg Remembered by William A. Sutton book review, published copy in Reserve: Western Reserve College Alumni Magazine, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Carl Sandburg Remembered by William A. Sutton book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Childhood's Unfinished Business" book review of Second Son by Stephen Stark, clipping from The New York Times Book Review, 1992 August 30 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "Cleveland International's Steve Popovich" essay, manuscript draft and published copy of Rolling Stone, 1980 June 12 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Creek Mary's Blood by Dee Brown book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - "Death Rattle" book review of Salvation on Sand Mountain by Dennis Covington, manuscript draft and The New York Times clipping, 1995 April 9 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - "The Debate: A Last Look Back" essay, manuscript draft and published copy in The North American Review, 1980 December (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Del Close Calls with Chicago's Eternal Second City" review, published copy in Crawdaddy magazine, 1978 June (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Destinies by Peter and Denne Bart book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Domesticity by Bob Shaccochis book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Drue Heinz Literature Prize, judge's comment sheets, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - The Duke of Deception: Memories of My Father by Geoffrey Wolff book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Dutch Treat by Tristan Jones and Ice Brothers by Sloan Wilson book reviews, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The Dying Animal by Philip Roth book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "Embracing the Venus de Milo" book review of Disarmed by Gregory Curtis, published copy in The News & Observer, 2003 December 28 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Enemies by Richard Harris book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Eyeing the Flash by Peter Fenton book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "A father's searing memoir of love" book review of The Boy and the Dog Are Sleeping by Nasdijj, published copy in The News & Observer, 2003 February 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "Favorite popular fiction writers" Esquire magazine prompt response, 1989 July (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - "Five from the Golden Age" book review, manuscript drafts, circa 1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Fool's Paradise" book review of Songs In Ordinary Time by Mary McGarry Morris, manuscript drafts and published copies of The Los Angeles Times Book Review, 1995 August (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "The Fourth Alarm" by John Cheever review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Frankenstein with a poet's bent" book review of My Life as a Fake by Peter Carey, published copy in The Herald, 2003 November 23 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Geronimo's Boys by Nasdijj book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Good News in a Season of Discomfort: Notes from an AP English Faculty Consultant" essay published in The College Board Review, photocopy, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Great Buffalo Hotel by Gordon Webber book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "Greetings from Flammable Cleveland" essay, published copy in Crawdaddy magazine, 1978 April (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - "A hand for Patrick amid the biggest disaster: love" book review of The Fourth Hand by John Irving, published copy in The Herald, 2001 July 8 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - hanging loose magazine review, manuscript draft and published copy in Serials Review, 1980 April-June (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - The Hill Bachelors by William Trevor book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Ice Brothers by Sloan Wilson book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "In the Hands of the Enemy" essay, manuscript drafts and published copy in Fiction Writer magazine, 2000 April (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "Irish-themed memoir is better than most" book review of HARP by John Gregory Dunne, published copy in The Plain Dealer, 1989 September 10 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - It Looked Like For Ever by Mark Harris book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Ivan Doig's 'local color' trip through Montana" book review of Ride With Me, Mariah Montana by Ivan Doig, manuscript drafts and published copy in The Chicago Tribune, 1990 September (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Jane Scott: too old for rock & roll?" music essay, published copy in Rolling Stone, 1979 May 17 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "The Jerry Garcia Feature: Dead Reckoning and Hamburger Metaphysics" music essay, published copy in Crawdaddy Feature magazine, 1979 March (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - L=A=N=G=U=A=G=E literary journal review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Lee K. Abbott on 'the most daunting book I read'" article in published copy of The News & Observer, 2001 October 7 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Libra by Don DeLillo book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Literary Monitor: The Voice of Contemporary Literature review published copy in Serials Review, 1981 January-March (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "Love in the Back 40" book review of Dancing at the Rascal Fair by Ivan Doig, published copy in The New York Times Book Review, 1987 November 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The Making of a Story by Alice LaPlante book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Marquand: An American Life by Millicent Bell book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "Marriage on the Killing Ground" book review column, published copy in Cleveland Magazine, 1978 September (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Mason & Dixon by Thomas Pynchon book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - "A master of long short story" book review of Selected Stories: Andre Dubus, manuscript drafts and published copy in The Plain Dealer, 1988 December 11 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - McKay's Bees by Thomas McMahon book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "Meanwhile, Back at the Ranch" essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - "Meditating on Guns, Love and Show Biz" book review of The Sharpshooter Blues by Lewis Nordan, manuscript drafts and published copy in The Herald, 1995 October (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Miramar Seduction by Keeling Jordan book review, manuscript draft and published copy in TWA Ambassador magazine, 1980 October (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Mom Kills Kids and Self by Alan Saperstein book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - "More of More" essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - My Drowning by Jim Grimsley book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Natural Order book review notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - "Necessary Heroes" essay, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Night of the Aurochs by Dalton Trumbo book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - "On the Cutting Edge" book reviews column, manuscript draft and published copy in Northern Ohio Live magazine, 1981 June 15-July 12 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "Painting both the light and dark sides of love" book review of In the Night Cafe by Joyce Johnson, manuscript drafts and published copy in The Plain Dealer, 1989 June 18 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Paradise Road book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - The Partisan by Benjamin Cheever book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Pete Dexter's mean streets" book review of Brotherly Love by Pete Dexter, published copy in the Chicago Tribune, 1991 October 13 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "A pinch of this and that in unruly India" book review of Real Time by Amit Chaudharri, published copy in The Herald, 2002 April 14 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - "Problems with contemporary short fiction" essay drafts, circa 2007 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - "Read Any Good Movies Lately?" book review column, published copy in Cleveland Magazine, 1978 May (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "Rejection" essay, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - "A rich, generous portrait of a troubled family" book review of Century's Son by Robert Boswell, published copy in The News & Observer, 2002 June 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - "Rick Bass seeks solace in snow-land" book review of Winter: Notes from Montana by Rick Bass, published copy in the Chicago Tribune, 1991 February 17 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Roads by Larry McMurty book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Second Son by Stephen Stark book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Serena by Ron Rash book review, manuscript draft, 2009 May 9 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - "Serious Fiction" essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "Seven Fictioneers" book reviews column, manuscript draft and published copy in Northern Ohio Live magazine, 1980 December 15-1981 January 11 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "Sexy Consuela and a fear of death send Kepesh right over the brink" book review of The Dying Animal by Philip Roth, published copy in The Herald, 2001 May 20 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Short Stuff" essay, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Sketches for a Life of Wassilly by Lydia Davis; Grammars for Jess/Twenty-two Cropped Sets by Marina LaPalma; and Special Offer by Jerry Bumpus book reviews, manuscript draft and published copy in The American Book Review, 1982 September-October (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - So There! by Nicole Louise Reid book review, draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Solo Faces by James Salter book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "Southern Exposure" book review of Southern Honor by Bertram Wyatt-Brown, published copy in Northern Ohio Live magazine, 1983 June (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Southern Writers Forum essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - "Speaking for Myself" essay, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "A step removed from madness" book review of You Are Not a Stranger Here by Adam Haslett, published copy in The News & Observer, 2002 August 11 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - "A Stubborn Sense of Place" response essay, manuscript draft, galley, and published copy in Harper's magazine, 1986 August (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "Stuff of dread and dream in contemporary Ireland" book review of The Hill Bachelors: Stories by William Trevor, published copy in The Herald, 2000 October 15 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "Success Eases Michael Stanley Band's 'Fear'" music essay, manuscript draft, and clipping from the Sun-Sentinel newspaper, 1981 October 12 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Summer Reading" essay, published copy in Cleveland Magazine, 1986 June (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "Talking Dirty" essay, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - "Thirteen Things About the Contemporary Short Story That Really Hack Me Off" essay, manuscript draft, undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Tinsel by William Goldman book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - To Skin a Cat by Thomas McGuane book review, manuscript draft and published copy in The Los Angeles Times Book Review, 1986 December 14 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "Travels with Larry in search of America" book review of Roads by Larry McMurty, published copy in The Herald, 2000 July 9 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "The Trite and the True" book review column, published copy in Cleveland Magazine, 1978 January (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "The True Story of Why I Do What I Do" essay, manuscript and published copies, 1988 March 17 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - "Truth pops out of the jack-in-the-box called life" book review for All the Days and Nights: The Collected Stories of William Maxwell, manuscript drafts and published copy in The Herald, 1995 January 22 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Twelve tales of woe from a China of Flying Pigeons" book review of The Bridegroom: Stories by Ha Jin, manuscript draft and published copy in The Herald, 2000 October 22 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - "Twenty Questions" essay included in Dog People collection, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Unsent Letters by Malcolm Bradbury book review, manuscript drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Vision Quest by Terry Davis book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - "V.S. Pritchett and the Short Story" book review column, manuscript draft and published copy in TWA Ambassador magazine, 1983 February (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "What the devil does in retirement" book review of Talk of the Devil by Riccardo Orizio, published copy in The News & Observer, 2003 May 18 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - "Widow Lauren poses in a fractured reality" book review of The Body Artist by Don DeLillo, published copy in The Herald, 2001 January 21 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Winding Stair by Douglas C. Jones book review, manuscript draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "Writer tends wounds with stories and song" book review of Geronimo's Bones by Nasdijj, published copies in The News & Observer, 2004 April 18 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - "A Writer's Congress:...and 2. Therefore" essay, published copy in The North American Review, 1981 December (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Writhing in the delirious affliction of love" book review of Love In the Time of Cholera by Gabriel Garcia Marquez, manuscript drafts and published copy in The Houston Post, 1988 April 24 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified essay drafts and notes, circa 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Untitled essays, undated (Box 23, Folder 27-28)
- Correspondence, 1977-2011; Series 3
  Correspondence contains letters and emails with publishers, colleagues, fellow writers, students, and academic institutions. Personal correspondence is also included. The arrangement of the correspondence is separated into three groups created by Lee Abbott, and is maintained in this series: the first group is chronological by the date the letters were sent, with one undated folder at the end of this group; the second group is arranged alphabetically by first letter of the name of the correspondent; and the third group is arranged alphabetically by the full name of the correspondent, or first name of the correspondent when a full name is unknown. Materials date from 1977 to 2011.
  - 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - 1993 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 1994 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 1995 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - 1996 January-June (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - 1996 August-December (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1999 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 2002 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 2003 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - 2005 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - A, 1981-1997 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - B, 1979-1998 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - C, 1977-1997 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - D, 1980-1998 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - E, 1979-1992 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - F, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - G, 1991-1998 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - H, 1980-1998 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - I, 1978-1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - J, 1986-1998 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - K, 1978-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - L, 1980-1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - M, 1979-1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - N, 1981-1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - O, 1987-1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - P, 1978-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Q, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - R, 1978-1994 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - S, 1978-1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - T, 1978-2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - U, 1980-1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - V, 1985-1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - W, 1977-2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Z, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Algonquin Books, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Alex, 1997 June 2 (Box 29, Folder 105)
  - Alix, 1997 March-April, September (Box 29, Folder 104, 106-108)
  - Amanda, 2009 December 16 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ann, 1997 September 13 (Box 29, Folder 109)
  - The Atlantic Monthly, 1984-1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Attfield (Hilary), 2011 June 13 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Barbara, 1997 March-April (Box 29, Folder 110-111)
  - Ben, 2008 December 15 (Box 29, Folder 112)
  - Benedict (Pinckney), 1987-1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Black Annie, 1997 September 8 (Box 29, Folder 113)
  - Bob, 1997 May 14 (Box 29, Folder 114)
  - Bosco (Ronald A.), 2005 November 9 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Brian, 2007 February 12 (Box 29, Folder 115)
  - Bruce, 2007 August 19 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Bryan, 1997 March 29 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Burrows (David), 2011 August 30 (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Busch (Frederick), 1980-2002 (Box 29, Folder 78-79, Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Carmen, 2007 March 11 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Carol, 1997 May 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Carpenter (Ken), 2008 March 12 (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - Cecilia, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 5-8)
  - Chimos, 2011 October 27 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Christine, 2008 July 23 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Claire, 2008 August 21 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Cole (Dave), 2005 June 26 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Comiskey (Diane), 2006 September 20 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Creamer (Stacy), 1990 April 27 (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - Dan, 1997 March 21-22 (Box 30, Folder 5-6)
  - Daniel, 1997 April 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Danielle, 2005 August, 2006 March (Box 28, Folder 11-13)
  - David, 2007 February 12 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Diane, 2007 February 2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Don, 1997 March 18 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Don, 2005 July 31 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Doris, 1997 April 13 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Doug, 2006 September 1 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Elaine Markson Literary Agency, Inc., 1978-2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Elizabeth, 2007 January 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Erica, 2006 July 6 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Fred, 1990-1997 (Box 29, Folder 82-83, Box 30, Folder 13-14)
  - Friends Committee and Centennial Committee, 2006 August 21 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Gardner (Leslie), 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Gee (E. Gordon), 2008 June 12 (Box 29, Folder 84)
  - Gene, 2006 June 20 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - The Georgia Review, 1979-1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Gina, 2008 August 29 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1985-1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Gupta (Prasenjit), 1997 April 13 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Gwynne, 2011 March 19 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Hall (Jim), 1990 March 19 (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - Hanrahan (Barbara), 1997 September 30 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Harrison (William), 1985-1998 (Box 20, Folder 21, Box 29, Folder 86)
  - Hempel (Amy), 1994 March 25 (Box 29, Folder 87)
  - Hodgman (John K.), 1993-2000 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Holly, 1997 April 16 (Box 29, Folder 88)
  - Holly, 2005 March-November (Box 28, Folder 20-22)
  - Janice, 1997 April 13 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Janice and John, 1997 April 11 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Jeff, 1997 May 14 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Jennifer, 2007 September-December (Box 28, Folder 23-28)
  - Jennifer, 2009 July 6 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Jennifer, 2011 March-April (Box 28, Folder 30-31)
  - Jesse, 1997 September 8 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Jill, 1997 May 23 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Jill and Evan, 2006 January 10 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Joan, 1997 April-August (Box 30, Folder 24-27)
  - Jollimore, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - John, 1997 September 8 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Johnson (Greg), 1990 February 12, June 25 (Box 29, Folder 89-90)
  - Jonathan, 1990 February 11 (Box 29, Folder 91)
  - Jonathan, 1997 October 26 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Judy, 2006 February 27 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Kathie, 1997-2010 (Box 28, Folder 34-69)
  - Kathy, 1997 May 9 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Kennedy (William), 1990 February 11 (Box 29, Folder 92)
  - Kim, 2010 June 14 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Laura, 1997 April 22 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Laurel, 2007 January-April (Box 28, Folder 71-73)
  - Laurie, 1997 March-October (Box 30, Folder 32-33, Box 28, Folder 74-81)
  - Lester (Neal A.), 2006 June 28 (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Lindberg (Stanley) editor, The Georgia Review, 1983-1988 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Lopez, 2006 July 11 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Louis, 1997 May 20 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Magnuson (Michael J.), 1992-1998 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Magnuson (Mike), 1994 January-February (Box 29, Folder 93-94)
  - Marie, 1997 August 7 (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - Mark, 1997 May 28 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Melanie, 1997 August 18 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Michael, 1997 March 30 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Mike, 1997 March-April (Box 28, Folder 83-85)
  - Miller (Joanna), 1997 June 4 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Mitch, undated (Box 28, Folder 86)
  - Moder (Carol), 2005 December 6 (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Munger (Roger), 2008 August 19 (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Murray, 2008 November 21 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Nancy, 1997 April 17 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Nancy, 2007 January 7 (Box 28, Folder 87)
  - Nick, 2007 April 16 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - The North American Review, 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - O'Connor (Phil), 1990 July 6 (Box 29, Folder 95)
  - The Ohio Review, 1978-1987 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Oliver (Mary), 1994 March 18 (Box 29, Folder 96)
  - Pamela, 2009 January-March (Box 28, Folder 88-96)
  - Patricia, 2008 August 26 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Paul, 1997 March 9 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Paula, 2008 July 25 (Box 28, Folder 97)
  - Penner (Jonathan), 1990 April-May (Box 29, Folder 97-98)
  - Perrotta (Tom), 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Peter, 1997 March 9 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Peter, 2007 February 6 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Queen B, 1997 August 28 (Box 28, Folder 98)
  - Raymond, 2009 July-August (Box 28, Folder 99-100)
  - Rebecca, 2004 March 15 (Box 28, Folder 101)
  - Rigby (Dale), 2007 October 23 (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - Roorbach (Bill); E. Gordon Gee; other Ohio State University colleagues, 1988-1998 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Royal (J.), 2009 April 12 (Box 28, Folder 102)
  - Sampson (Scott A.), 1997 September 2 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Siebenshuh (William R.), 2006 August 15 (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - Shirley, 1990 January 22 (Box 29, Folder 99)
  - Smith (Bruce R.), 2007 September 10 (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Smith (Sidonie), 2007 August 20 (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Southern Methodist University Press, 1981-1998 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Spencer (Darrell), 1992-2002 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Stacy, 1990 July 23 (Box 29, Folder 100)
  - Stefanie, 2007 June 13 (Box 28, Folder 103)
  - Steve and Bonnie, 2006 August 21 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Tabachnik (Stephen), 2006 July 10 (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - Thon (Melanie Rae), 1996-1999 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Tim, 1994 January-February (Box 29, Folder 101-102)